{"quiz":[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What did the author of the book study?",
    "options": {
      "A": "B.Sc (Ed) Mathematics",
      "B": "B.A English Language",
      "C": "B.A Literary Studies",
      "D": "BSc Political Science"
    },
    "correct": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "The book described Talle as a?",
    "options": {
      "A": "The precious child",
      "B": "The quiet one",
      "C": "The friendly child",
      "D": "The holy child"
    },
    "correct": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Who was Omar's immediate sister?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Ummi",
      "B": "Omar",
      "C": "Salma",
      "D": "Teemah"
    },
    "correct": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Ummi's husband wanted to study law but the providence chose that he study _____",
    "options": {
      "A": "commerce",
      "B": "accounting",
      "C": "law",
      "D": "history"
    },
    "correct": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "The full meaning of IPO is ______",
    "options": {
      "A": "Independent Police Officer",
      "B": "International Police Officer",
      "C": "Investigating Police Officer",
      "D": "Investigative Police Officer"
    },
    "correct": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is Ummi's Occupation?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Trader",
      "B": "Teacher",
      "C": "Business woman",
      "D": "Nurse"
    },
    "correct": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What is Ummi Matric Number?",
    "options": {
      "A": "UG0001",
      "B": "UG00001",
      "C": "UG001",
      "D": "UG0011"
    },
    "correct": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is full meaning of EMEC?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Examination Malpractice and Ethics Committee",
      "B": "Examining Malpractice and Ethics Committee",
      "C": "Examination Malpractice and Ethics Convention",
      "D": "Examination Management and Ethics Committee"
    },
    "correct": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is the full name of Salma?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Salma Mohammed",
      "B": "Salma Johnson",
      "C": "Salma Samuel",
      "D": "Salma Ahmed"
    },
    "correct": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Who was the narrator of The Life Changer?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Salma",
      "B": "Ummi",
      "C": "Omar",
      "D": "Bint"
    },
    "correct": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "How old is Bint?",
    "options": {
      "A": "6 years old",
      "B": "4 years old",
      "C": "5 years old",
      "D": "7 years old"
    },
    "correct": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What question did Bint ask her teacher?",
    "options": {
      "A": "How to say good morning",
      "B": "How to say what is your name",
      "C": "How to say you're welcome",
      "D": "How to say that's very good"
    },
    "correct": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Who were the people in the car?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Lawal and Labaran",
      "B": "Habib and Labaran",
      "C": "Lawal and Kabir",
      "D": "Labara and Zarki"
    },
    "correct": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "How much did Habib give Tomiwa personally?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Ten thousand naira",
      "B": "Five Thousand Naira",
      "C": "Thirty thousand naira",
      "D": "Twenty Thousand naira"
    },
    "correct": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "How much did Tomiwa give her roommates?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Five thousand naira",
      "B": "Ten thousand Naira",
      "C": "Fifteen thousand Naira",
      "D": "Twenty thousand naira"
    },
    "correct": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What was Omar's JAMB exam?",
    "options": {
      "A": "230",
      "B": "250",
      "C": "220",
      "D": "260"
    },
    "correct": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What is the full meaning of the acronym EMAL?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Examination Malpractice",
      "B": "Examination misconduct",
      "C": "Examination management",
      "D": "Examination Manners"
    },
    "correct": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Who introduced the snail delicacy?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Salma",
      "B": "Ngozi",
      "C": "Ada",
      "D": "Tomiwa"
    },
    "correct": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "\"Nothing happened, My friend didn't feel like giving you her number so she gave you mine instead\" Who is the friend?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Salma",
      "B": "Ada",
      "C": "Tomiwa",
      "D": "Ngozi"
    },
    "correct": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "It might be said that there is some kind of sibling rivalry between",
    "options": {
      "A": "Teemah and Bint",
      "B": "Teemah and Omar",
      "C": "Jamila and Omar",
      "D": "Jamila and Teemah"
    },
    "correct": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "One reason the narrator had the habit of entering her children's room unannounced was because",
    "options": {
      "A": "to monitor their hygiene and tidiness",
      "B": "to monitor their prayer life",
      "C": "to check on their welfare",
      "D": "to keep them studying their books"
    },
    "correct": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "According to the story, one of the following is true",
    "options": {
      "A": "Tomiwa and Ngozi are neighbours",
      "B": "Ada and Salma are course mates",
      "C": "Salma and Tomiwa are rivals",
      "D": "Salma and Tomiwa are roommates"
    },
    "correct": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "Early in which month did the southwest monsoon break?",
    "options": {
      "A": "August",
      "B": "May",
      "C": "July",
      "D": "June"
    },
    "correct": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What was Baby's real name?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Navomi Ipe",
      "B": "Estha",
      "C": "Rachel",
      "D": "Kochamma"
    },
    "correct": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "From the words lettered A to D, choose the word that rhymes with the given word: Prison",
    "options": {
      "A": "rising",
      "B": "risen",
      "C": "potion",
      "D": "motion"
    },
    "correct": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "From the words lettered A to D, choose the word that rhymes with the given word: Crate",
    "options": {
      "A": "Great",
      "B": "Mint",
      "C": "Creek",
      "D": "Treat"
    },
    "correct": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "From the words lettered A to D, choose the word that rhymes with the given word: Phone",
    "options": {
      "A": "frown",
      "B": "grown",
      "C": "gown",
      "D": "brown"
    },
    "correct": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "Choose the word that has a different stress pattern",
    "options": {
      "A": "embrace",
      "B": "suspect(V)",
      "C": "member",
      "D": "project(V)"
    },
    "correct": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "Choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined: Watched",
    "options": {
      "A": "lived",
      "B": "address",
      "C": "letter",
      "D": "match"
    },
    "correct": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "In each of the following sentences, the word that receives the emphatic stress is written in capital letters. From the options lettered A to D, choose the appropriate answer: John's watch is made of GOLD.",
    "options": {
      "A": "Whose watch is made of gold?",
      "B": "What is made of gold?",
      "C": "Is John's watch made of silver?",
      "D": "Is John's necklace made of gold?"
    },
    "correct": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "In each of the following sentences, the word that receives the emphatic stress is written in capital letters. From the options lettered A to D, choose the one which is the appropriate answer: She WORKS at the hospital.",
    "options": {
      "A": "Who works at the hospital?",
      "B": "Where does she work?",
      "C": "Does she work at the hospital?",
      "D": "What does she do at the hospital?"
    },
    "correct": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "In each of the following sentences, the word that receives the emphatic stress is written in capital letters. From the options lettered A to D, choose the one which is the appropriate answer: Aderonke STATED she had a right to her privacy.",
    "options": {
      "A": "Did Aderonke lament she had a right to her privacy?",
      "B": "Did Omowunmi state she had a right to her privacy?",
      "C": "Did Aderonke state she had a right to his privacy?",
      "D": "Did Aderonke state she had a right to her openness?"
    },
    "correct": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "Choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined: National",
    "options": {
      "A": "sugar",
      "B": "raise",
      "C": "glass",
      "D": "tree"
    },
    "correct": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "Identify the word that has the stress on the first syllable",
    "options": {
      "A": "Hotel",
      "B": "Esteem",
      "C": "Police",
      "D": "Table"
    },
    "correct": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "From the options lettered A-D, choose the option that is most nearly opposite in meaning to the underlined word: Twice, he was repulsed with heavy losses",
    "options": {
      "A": "repelled",
      "B": "gratified",
      "C": "irated",
      "D": "shocked"
    },
    "correct": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "I only visited Chidi. This means that",
    "options": {
      "A": "None of the above",
      "B": "I didn't do anything aside from visiting Chidi",
      "C": "I didn't go with anyone to visit Chidi",
      "D": "I visited Chidi and his friends"
    },
    "correct": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "From the options lettered A-D, choose the option that is most nearly opposite in meaning to the underlined word: My father is parsimonious",
    "options": {
      "A": "thrifty",
      "B": "ungenerous",
      "C": "frugal",
      "D": "generous"
    },
    "correct": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "From the options lettered A-D, choose the option that is most nearly opposite in meaning to the underlined word: Last Easter was an austere period.",
    "options": {
      "A": "harsh",
      "B": "severe",
      "C": "prosperous",
      "D": "sour"
    },
    "correct": "C"
  }
]
}